All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
There, they found themselves facing the new Fishman pirates, who were looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom and instigated an all-out war.
Luffy and his friends thwarted their plans, but soon became wrapped up in the affairs of another dangerous pirate, Big Mom of the Four Emperors.
Forget Fishman Island!
Now that you've chosen to go against me, I'll just have to get my revenge on you instead!
Well then, Monkey D. Luffy, now that I know who you are, come here. Let's check in the New World!
Sure thing, be there soon. I've got something I need to settle with you too.
Hmm?
I like this island. It's too risky to trust you with it.
Once I get there, I'm gonna kick your ass!
And then I'll make Fishman Island my territory!
Little brat!
Many problems lie ahead. A trap awaiting in the New World.
Here.
Oh, thanks.
It's some of our famous kelp tea. Please give it a try.
It helps with digestion, so it'll do you good after that big meal.
It's great! Thanks for all the hospitality, Minister.
Yes, you've treated us so generously. I just hope we have an inconvenience to you.
Oh, no. There are no words to describe my gratitude for what you all have done for Fishman Island.
This is the least I can do.
Man, it's too bad we have to get out of here soon, huh?
Please don't talk about leaving the island, Usopp! I'm not ready to say goodbye to you!
Don't cry! I'm sorry, okay?
And it's Usopp.
Oh. Hey, where'd Frankie run off to?
He went to figure out something with the ship earlier.
Apparently, there's some trick he needs to learn to get us back up to the surface.
Ugh.
Oh, yes. This must be the list of valuables that were stolen out of the treasure chamber.
My goodness. This is more than I thought. The tamate box, too?
Wait, that means...
That means I'll be the king of the ship.
Ah!
Oh!
Uh!
Straw hat. Of course he'd show up. If not for him, I would be rich by now.
Oh, well. It wasn't a total loss, at least. Still got plenty of treasure in me.
treasure in me. Now I'll buy about a hundred pirate ships so when I get to the new world I can wipe
out those damn straw hats. What? It's gone! How could someone steal my stolen gold? I can't even afford
a piece of candy to soothe my sorrows now! My dear, sweet, precious treasure! Mark my words, I will find you!
By the way, Jinbei, since we haven't spoken in some time, might you tell me how the Sun Pirates are faring?
Quite well. In fact, they have so much energy I can scarcely keep up with them sometimes.
Hmm. If I may be perfectly frank with you, I never imagined that the Sun Pirates would
align themselves with Big Mom. I was quite taken aback by the news, but perhaps that is my ignorance speaking.
Do you believe it's a wise decision? Big Mom is ruthless, but she lets us do as we please.
It's fine for now. Hmm. I see. Then if I may be frank once more, it surprises me that you're
comfortable taking orders from anyone other than Fish or Tiger. No, it's alright. I'm not above
working under someone else's authority by any means. That's the way it works in the new world. If a
captain wishes to guarantee the safety of his crew, allying with the four emperors is the best way to do it.
Is that all? It seems to me that you're doing it for the good of Fishman Island as well. Even after
Whitebeard's passing, our kingdom remains safe under Big Mom's protection because you connected us with
her. We can't thank you enough for that, Jinbei. Oh no. Please don't thank me. We have a responsibility
to make sure Fishman Island is protected. Even if we are wanted criminals.
Having said that, I believe that the time may have come for me to terminate my partnership with Big Mom.
Ah, so you're going to accept Luffy's invitation.
Hey, Jinbei. What do you say, pal? Will you join my crew?
Yes. I have made my decision. But the pirate world operates through honor, not contracts.
We'd much rather make a verbal agreement over drinks than sign documents. Because of that,
we mustn't go breaking such agreements without careful consideration. What concerns me the most
is the possibility that Big Mom will direct your anger at Fishman Island.
Honestly, Jinbei. You need not feel responsible for every little thing.
If such an incident comes to pass, then so be it. I have a plan. Why, just today we took in 70,000
fierce newcomers from Fishman District. They'll make fine soldiers. Do not worry about us, Jamal.
And in the event we lose the protection of Big Mom's Jolly Roger, there is another flag I'd like to use instead.
One with a straw hat might look nice, don't you think, Jamal?
Couldn't agree more. I'm partial to that flag myself.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Your Majesty!
Forgive me, but we have a serious problem.
Hm?
It's terrible.
What's the matter, Minister of the Right?
I remember something from long ago.
With all due respect, sir, we made a mistake by letting the straw hat pirates keep that stolen treasure.
Hm?
I'm not certain if they found it yet, but if they do, could you please ask them to give the Tomate Box back to us?
How dare you! I could never ask them to return a gift that we gave them for saving us!
I know, but...
If they open it, it'll explode! Why would you do such a thing?
I'm sorry, but you see, after the Tomate Box was stolen ten years ago,
I figured if another thief were to take it, we ought to teach them a lesson.
I decided to rig the box with explosives that would detonate as soon as the box was opened.
It seemed like a good idea at the time.
But I was wrong, and since I'm in charge of the Tomate Box and the rest of the treasure chamber, I...
Very well, I understand.
If Luffy and the others return with the treasures,
please explain the situation and take the Tomate Box back before someone gets hurt.
I do apologize.
Oh, dear.
But there's still a chance that they'll open it before they get back.
Yes, that concerns me as well.
Your Majesty, Minister, an update.
Luffy and the others have just returned.
Ah, so they made it back safely.
That's excellent.
It appears I was worried over nothing.
What?
Huh?
You gave the treasure?
To Big Mom?
Luffy!
I had to.
She was going to wreck the whole island because she didn't get any candy.
What is her problem?
I mean, if it was meat, I'd understand.
Don't worry.
I already handled it.
Because I picked up that snail and gave her a piece of my mind.
Seriously?
Yeah, but no one talks back to her.
My, that's wonderful.
Well, you sure are brave, Luffy.
Don't encourage him.
This isn't a good thing.
Please don't yell at me, Nusa.
I told you it's Usa.
Whatever.
I'm sorry.
Oh, Luffy.
What have you done now?
I'd better sever my bond with Big Mom before this gets any more complicated.
I understand this may be difficult, especially for your hard-headed captain, but please refrain
from agitating her anymore.
No joke!
She's one of the four emperors and I'm way too young to die!
This is even worse than we feared.
What are we going to do now?
If Big Mom gets that tomate box and she opens it herself, it's going to blow up in her face
and then we're screwed!
She'll think Straw Hat's trying to start dribble and then there'll be a war on her hands.
We mustn't let that happen!
Well, it's not like you had any other choice, right?
Yeah, it's already been done now.
Guess you kind of had to stand up to her.
I suppose I can't really be upset at you over that.
Exactly!
I couldn't just let her punish these guys for...
That's my girl.
Still!
I can't believe you gave her all of this treasure!
NUMMY!
I'll put you out!
You did that already!
Okay, here it goes.
To the new world!
We're all going to die!
I'm already dead, but...
Meanwhile, not far from the candy factory...
Damn it all!
Someone must have picked up the treasures and ran when I was knocked out on the ground!
Whoever the thief may be, I'll make sure they suffer for what they've done!
All I have to do now is confront those pickpockets and take the riches back again.
With that and the new information about the mermaid princess, I can make a good impression for sure!
Wait a minute!
Who are they and what have they got in those bags?
Straw hat Luffy, huh?
What makes that punk think he can pick a fight with Mama?
Mais oui, the monsieur does have a certain je ne sais quoi.
She must be furious, sir.
The tea party's in four days.
I say we get her as many treats as we can on the way back.
We can't fix it, but hopefully we can soften the blow.
At least a little bit.
Indeed.
Hopefully a detente will be adequate, and I am sure the treasures won't hurt.
I knew it!
Those are mine!
Just wait till I catch you two!
I'll bury you alive!
I stole those treasures once!
That means I can steal them again!
Pardon?
I feel like I've seen that ugly mug before.
Get out!
There he is!
It says here he's an up-and-comer.
Goes by the name Wet-Head Caribou.
Get out!
Oh!
So he's worth 200 million!
Great!
Just when we thought this was over!
He he he!
It's too late for you to beg for mercy!
Swamp, swamp, cat Lincoln!
Sorry, boys!
That's what happens when you steal from me!
This is crazy!
He he he he!
He he he he he!
Huh?
Wait, what?
A turtle?
They are here!
He he he he he!
A turtle?
A tank?
What?
Oh!
A little big tiger!
Who cares?
You don't scare me!
People with low-gear double fruit powers always end up dying young.
You fools think that power makes you invincible.
Gidda!
Half-ball challenges are très disappointing.
Allons-y, monsieur Pecum's.
Mama's waiting.
That guy's worth 200 million, and he just...
If I remember, Pecum's has a bounty of 330 million.
That's pretty scary, and Big Mom probably makes what he just did look like child's play.
I sure hope Luffy knows what he's doing.
This is quite a send-off.
There's the Sonny!
Yeah! I see Frankie!
He looks like he's ready to set sail.
Hey! Frankie!
I can't wait.
And somewhere near the Red Line, in the waters of the New World.
We're seeing you.
Merchant report from headquarters.
Several coded ships are ascending from the seafloor at high speed.
All hands distinctions now.
I repeat, everyone get to your posts quickly!
That's a pirate ship!
There's another one at two o'clock!
Fire ships are popping up all over the place, sir!
What the hell is this?
Trying to get on our good side, you suck-up?
Mind your own business!
They finally set me free from that living hell!
I can't die now!
Here comes the big one!
Captain, look out!
I'll shield you from harm, Captain!
Get out of the way!
I want to do it!
Move!
I've got it!
Woo!
That's our captain for ya!
That was really beautiful, Captain!
Yeah, and the swordplay wasn't half bad either!
Are you taking this seriously or not?
Every one of you should know how to deflect a bombshell!
There was never a better time to use that skill than just now, so-
Um, that's a mast.
Here, I cleaned your glasses for you!
Thank you.
She's so cute!
She's like a flower among this filthy crew!
You know, I'd die for you in a heartbeat, Captain!
Yeah, me too!
Don't fool around in the middle of combat!
You'll get yourselves killed!
The G5 is such a joke!
And to think you're all Navy soldiers!
You had better not take me lightly just because I'm a woman!
Oh, Captain Toshigi!
You're just so adorable!
How can I not respect you?
That's exactly the kind of treatment I mean!
There's a difference between respect and whatever you-
Keep it down, Toshigi.
I'm busy.
My apologies, sir.
I see.
So a pirate from the seafloor named Horty Jones took you captive.
That explains a lot.
That must be why there were no rookies passing through Fishman Island recently.
Took us captive?
I wish!
He made us his slaves!
Horty stirred up some kind of civil war on Fishman Island!
He made us fight for his side!
And then this group of pirates set us free!
A group of pirates?
Yeah!
But I'm not telling you who!
Don't be stupid!
Can't you see who we're dealing with?
They're not just Navy soldiers!
They're the G5!
They use pirates as bait when they fish for sharks!
Or even as kindling for a bonfire!
They're the rogue unit of the Navy!
They don't even obey orders from HQ!
Trust me, you have no idea how ruthless these bastards are!
Of all the people to be caught by, we had to end up in the hands of the notorious White Chase Smoker!
Well, Vice Admiral, can we take over from here?
No, I beg you!
I'll tell you everything!
Please have mercy!
The ones who defeated Horty Jones and his crew!
It was the Straw Hat Pirates, okay?!
I know that already, idiot!
Filled with both excitement and trepidation, the crew finally sets sail for the new world!
After bidding their fond farewells, the Straw Hats leave with a new log pose in hand!
Luffy makes a promise to the tearful Shira Hoshi and recalls an old vow he made to Shanks!
Overcoming trials and tragedies, Luffy's dream is on course once again!
On the next, One Piece!
Finally time to go!
Goodbye, Fishman Island!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!